(Leonard:)Yeah.
(Sheldon:)So, what are some ways we
could set our comic book store
(Sheldon:)apart from the
competition?
(Leonard:)Oh, kids buy comic books.
It would be great
(Leonard:)to figure out a way
to get more kids in the store.
(Howard:)You know, when I was a
kid, I loved going there,
(Howard:)but I could
never get a ride.
(Raj:)Ooh, what if we got a van and
drove around and picked kids up?
(Emily:)Nice.
(Sheldon:)You mean,
like at parks and schools?
(Howard:)Toy stores,
puppet shows.
(Leonard:)Hold on. So, your idea is
to get a van
(Leonard:)and cruise the streets looking
for kids to pick up?
(Sheldon:)Yes.
(Leonard:)And are you gonna use candy
to lure them in?
We are now!
(Penny:)You told Emily
we hooked up?!